This is Adrienne Felt.
这是 Adrienne Felt
Adrienne is a PhD student at Berkeley, and she's done a lot of interesting work
Adrienne Felt 是加州大学伯克利分校的博士生 她做了很多有趣的工作
on computer security.
有关于计算机安全的工作
So what do our students need to understand about security?
关于安全性 我们的学生需要了解什么？
One of the first projects I looked at, which I actually worked here with Dr. Evans,
我做的第一个项目 事实上我是与 Evans 博士合作的
was I use Facebook and I install and use Facebook applications.
这一项目就是我使用 Facebook 安装并使用 Facebook 应用程序
Many of you may be familiar with the Washington Post Social Reader.
你们当中很多人可能熟悉华盛顿邮报社交阅读器
And at the time I was just curious.
当时我只是好奇
What are these doing with my data? How are they getting my data?
这些与我的数据有什么关系呢？他们怎么得到我数据的呢？
How do these things work?
这些东西是如何运作的？
And so I decided to learn more about how they work,
于是我决定进一步了解他们是如何运作的
and from there it led to basically what ended up becoming my thesis topic in a PhD program.
就这样 这最终成了我博士学位项目的论文主题
I'm still interested in how do applications get data and how do they use the data.
我仍然对应用软件如何获得数据和应用程序如何使用的数据很感兴趣
When developers are writing applications that access users' private information
当开发人员正在编写获得用户私人信息
or resources like their location or their camera,
或资源的应用程序时 如用户位置或相机
they need to keep in mind that they need to a) respect users' privacy
开发人员需要记住 第一 他们需要尊重用户的隐私
and only use the resources that they need to use,
仅使用他们需要的资源
and b) they have to be careful to build their applications in such a way
第二 他们要小心 使应用建立的程序
that they don't accidentally leak this data to other applications.
不会向其他应用程序意外泄漏数据
So I primarily focus on Android development and security of Android applications.
所以我主要关注 Android 的开发和 Android 应用程序的安全
One thing that's really important for an Android application developer to know
Android 应用程序开发人员需要知道的一件重要的事是
is about the privacy and security of their applications.
是应用程序隐私的安全
So when a user installs an application from the Android Market,
因此 当用户从 Android 市场安装一个应用程序
they're shown things called permissions, which are small warnings
他们会看到权限的小警告
that tell the user about all of the resources that the application gets access to on their phone.
告诉用户 应用程序能从他们手机上获取的所有资源
For example, for this application I'm looking at,
例如 我正在看的这个应用程序
the application can get access to location, the Internet, the list of contacts, camera, etc.
可以获取到用户的位置、互联网、列表中的联系人、相机等信息
So the user is warned before the application installation is completed
因此 在应用程序安装完成之前警告用户
that the application can do all of these things.
应用程序可以执行所有这些事情
So as a developer, it's important to only ask for access
对开发人员来说 只要求获取
to resources that your application really needs.
你的应用程序真正需要的资源 是非常重要的
Otherwise you might unnecessarily scare off users
否则 你可能会吓跑
who might otherwise want to install your application.
那些可能想安装你的应用程序的用户
So one of the projects we built was a static analysis tool
我们建立的其中一个项目 是一个静态分析工具
that analyzes the permission usage of Android applications
分析 Android 应用程序使用的权限
so that it can warn developers if developers are requesting more permissions
这样 如果开发人员在请求
than they actually need for their applications to work.
比应用程序运行实际需要的更多的权限时 它会警告开发人员